* High Contrast

Close Menu

Privacy Policy
==============

Last modified: December 13, 2024

### Introduction

Alternative Behavior Strategies, LLC d/b/a ABS Kids and its affiliated companies, ABS Psychology Services California, P.C, ABS Utah, P.C. (“Company” or “We”) and ABS Kids, P.C., respect your privacy and are committed to protecting it through our compliance with this policy. 

This policy describes the types of information we may collect from you or that you may   
provide: 1) when you visit the websites: [https://abskids.com](https://abskids.com/), [https://absfamilies.com](https://absfamilies.com/), or 2) when ABS employees or contractors visit the ABS Virtual Office (collectively, our “Website”). This policy describes our practices for collecting, using, maintaining, protecting, and disclosing that information.

* This policy applies to information we collect: 

* On this Website. 
* In email, text, and other electronic messages between you and this Website. 
* Information we collect from on our website from our following webpages:
    * “Get Started”
    * “Insurance Information”

It does not apply to information collected by:

* us offline or through any other means, including on any other website operated by Company or any third party; or 
* any third party, including through any application or content (including advertising) that may link to or be accessible from or on the Website. 

Please read this policy carefully to understand our policies and practices regarding your   
information and how we will treat it. If you do not agree with our policies and practices, your choice is not to use our Website. By accessing or using this Website, you agree to this privacy policy. This policy may change from time to time (see Changes to Our Privacy Policy). Your continued use of this Website after we make changes is deemed to be acceptance of those changes, so please check the policy periodically for updates.

### Children Under the Age of 13

Our Website is not intended for children under 13 years of age. No one under age 13   
may provide any information to or on the Website. We do not knowingly collect personal   
information from children under 13. If you are under 13, do not use or provide any information on this Website or on or through any of its features. If we learn we have collected or received personal information from a child under 13 without verification of parental consent, we will delete that information. 

### Information We Collect About You and How We Collect It

We collect several types of information from and about users of our Website, including   
information: 

* Information by which you may be personally identified, such as your name, the patient’s name, postal address, e-mail address, telephone number, or any other identifier by which you may be contacted online or offline (“personal information”); 
* that is about you but individually does not identify you; and/or 
* name of your insurance company; 

* indicated interest in our services; 
* indicated questions about your coverage; 
* indicated preferred time to be called; and, 
* about your internet connection, the equipment you use to access our Website and usage details. 

We collect this information:

* Directly from you when you provide it to us. 
* Automatically as you navigate through the site. Information collected automatically may include usage details, IP addresses, and information collected through cookies, web beacons, and other tracking technologies. 
* From third parties, for example, our business partners. 

### Information You Provide to Us.

The information we collect on or through our Website may include:

* Information that you provide by filling in forms on our Website. This includes information provided at the time of requesting further services. We may also ask you for information when you report a problem with our Website. 
* Records and copies of your correspondence (including email addresses), if you contact us. 
* Information provided by you in the intake packet, which may include your address, phone number, email, and other contact information.

You also may provide information to be published or displayed (hereinafter, “**posted**“) on public areas of the Website, or transmitted to other users of the Website or third parties (collectively, “**User Contributions**“). Your User Contributions are posted on and transmitted to others at your own risk. Although we limit access to certain pages, please be aware that no security measures are perfect or impenetrable. Additionally, we cannot control the actions of other users of the Website with whom you may choose to share your User Contributions. Therefore, we cannot and do not guarantee that your User Contributions will not be viewed by unauthorized persons. 

### Information We Collect Through Automatic Data Collection Technologies.

As you navigate through and interact with our Website, we may use automatic data collection technologies to collect certain information about your equipment, browsing actions, and patterns, including: 

* Details of your visits to our Website, including traffic data, location data, logs, and other communication data and the resources that you access and use on the Website. 
* Information about your computer and internet connection, including your IP address, operating system, and browser type. 

We also may use these technologies to collect information about your online activities   
over time and across third-party websites or other online services (behavioral tracking). 

The information we collect automatically may include personal information or we may   
maintain it or associate it with personal information we collect in other ways or receive from third parties. It helps us to improve our Website and to deliver a better and more personalized service, including by enabling us to: 

* Estimate our audience size and usage patterns. 

* Store information about your preferences, allowing us to customize our Website according to your individual interests. 
* Speed up your searches. 
* Recognize you when you return to our Website

The technologies we use for this automatic data collection may include:

* **Cookies (or browser cookies).** A cookie is a small file placed on the hard drive of your computer. You may refuse to accept browser cookies by activating the appropriate setting on your browser. However, if you select this setting you may be unable to access certain parts of our Website. Unless you have adjusted your browser setting so that it will refuse cookies, our system will issue cookies when you direct your browser to our Website. 

* **Flash Cookies.** Certain features of our Website may use local stored objects (or Flash cookies) to collect and store information about your preferences and navigation to, from, and on our Website. Flash cookies are not managed by the same browser settings as are used for browser cookies. For information about managing your privacy and security settings for Flash cookies, see Choices About How We Use and Disclose Your Information. 
* **Web Beacons.** Pages of our Website may contain small electronic files known as web beacons (also referred to as clear gifs, pixel tags, and single-pixel gifs) that permit the Company, for example, to count users who have visited those pages and for other related website statistics (for example, recording the popularity of certain website content and verifying system and server integrity). 

### Third-Party Use of Cookies and Other Tracking Technologies.

Some content or applications, including advertisements, on the Website are served by   
third-parties, including advertisers, ad networks and servers, content providers, and application providers. These third parties may use cookies alone or in conjunction with web beacons or other tracking technologies to collect information about you when you use our website. The information they collect may be associated with your personal information or they may collect information, including personal information, about your online activities over time and across different websites and other online services. They may use this information to provide you with interest-based (behavioral) advertising or other targeted content. 

We do not control these third parties’ tracking technologies or how they may be used. If   
you have any questions about an advertisement or other targeted content, you should contact the responsible provider directly. For information about how you can opt out of receiving targeted advertising from many providers, see Choices About How We Use and Disclose Your   
Information. 

### How We Use Your Information

We use information that we collect about you or that you provide to us, including any   
personal information:

* To present our Website and its contents to you. 
* To provide you with information, products, or services that you request from us. 
* To fulfill any other purpose for which you provide it. 

* To carry out our obligations and enforce our rights arising from any contracts entered into between you and us, including for billing and collection. 
* To notify you about changes to our Website or any products or services we offer or provide though it. 
* In any other way we may describe when you provide the information. 
* For internal treatment, operational, or billing purposes. 
* For any other purpose with your consent. 

We may also use your information to contact you about goods and services that may be  
of interest to you.

### Disclosure of Your Information

We may disclose aggregated information about our users, and information that does not  
identify any individual, without restriction.

We may disclose personal information that we collect or you provide as described in this  
privacy policy:

* We do not sell, rent, lease, or otherwise transfer your phone number to any third parties without your consent, or as otherwise permitted by law.
* Your phone number may be shared with our affiliates, subsidiaries, or partner companies for related services but not for marketing purposes. **SMS consent will not be shared.**
* Within our organization, access to your phone number is restricted to employees who need it to provide you with our SMS service**.** 

* To contractors, service providers, and other third parties we use to support our business. 
* To a buyer or other successor in the event of a merger, divestiture, restructuring, reorganization, dissolution, or other sale or transfer of some or all of Company’s assets, whether as a going concern or as part of bankruptcy, liquidation, or similar proceeding, in which personal information held by Company about our Website users is among the assets transferred. 
* To fulfill the purpose for which you provide it. 
* For any other purpose disclosed by us when you provide the information. 
* With your consent. 

We may also disclose your personal information:

* To comply with any court order, law, or legal process, including to respond to any government or regulatory request. 
* To comply with other agreements, including for billing and collection purposes. 
* If we believe disclosure is necessary or appropriate to protect the rights, property, or safety of the Company, our customers, or others.

SMS Opt-Out Information

* You may opt-out by replying STOP or ask for more information by replying HELP. Message frequency varies. Message and data rates may apply. You may review our Privacy Policy to learn how your data is used. 
* You may opt out of receiving SMS messages at any time by replying with “STOP” to any SMS message you receive from us. After opting out, you will receive a confirmation message, and we will cease sending SMS messages to your number.
* If you need assistance or have questions about our SMS service, reply with “HELP” to any SMS message you receive, or contact our customer support team at 800-434-8923.

### Choices About How We Use and Disclose Your Information

We strive to provide you with choices regarding the personal information you provide to  
us. We have created mechanisms to provide you with the following control over your  
information:

* **Tracking Technologies and Advertising.** You can set your browser to refuse all or some browser cookies, or to alert you when cookies are being sent. To learn how you can manage your Flash cookie settings, visit the Flash player settings page on Adobe’s website. If you disable or refuse cookies, please note that some parts of this site may then be inaccessible or not function properly.  
    
* We do not control third parties’ collection or use of your information to serve interest-based advertising. However, these third parties may provide you with ways to choose not to have your information collected or used in this way.

### Data Security

We have implemented measures designed to secure your personal information from   
accidental loss and from unauthorized access, use, alteration, and disclosure.

The safety and security of your information also depends on you. Where we have given   
you (or where you have chosen) a password for access to certain parts of our Website, you are responsible for keeping this password confidential. We ask you not to share your password with anyone. We urge you to be careful about giving out information in public areas of the Website like message boards. The information you share in public areas may be viewed by any user of the Website. 

Unfortunately, the transmission of information via the internet is not completely secure.   
Although we do our best to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee the security of your personal information transmitted to our Website. Any transmission of personal information is at your own risk. We are not responsible for circumvention of any privacy settings or security measures contained on the Website. 

### Changes to Our Privacy Policy

It is our policy to post any changes we make to our privacy policy on this page with a   
notice that the privacy policy has been updated on the Website home page. If we make material changes to how we treat our users’ personal information, we will notify you through a notice on the Website home page. The date the privacy policy was last revised is identified at the top of the page. You are responsible for ensuring we have an up-to-date active and deliverable email address for you, and for periodically visiting our Website and this privacy policy to check for any changes. 

### Contact Information

To ask questions or comment about this privacy policy and our privacy practices, contact us at: [\[email protected\]](https://www.abskids.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection). 

Have a Question?
----------------

Find a Location
---------------

[\[email protected\]](https://www.abskids.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)

888-391-4987

[\[email protected\]](https://www.abskids.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)

Also of Interest:

© 2024 Alternative Behavior Strategies, LLC d/b/a ABS Kids. All rights reserved.
